I just don't I don't know how don't get
ki so this is this blew my mind this is
a real sign I saw four missing cat one
time pole somewhere
he said missing cat and had a picture of
some dumb cat you know and then said
reward $2,000 - first of all cats are
free I'm pretty sure right I mean these
guys must be $2,000 for his old cat all
right I don't want to judge I'll say
this if I lost my cat if I accidentally
lost our cats I would put up signs - I
would I would I would have to my sense
would be different though my signs would
say missing two cats reward two cats
all right I'm losing you I can feel
there are more there are more cat people
in here than this weirdo and a couple
weirdoes over that's fine that's fine
[Applause]
I get it you love your cats and I'm the
bad guy you know what else this is it
here this maybe this will make sense to
you you know what it is it's the cat
hairball
okay I didn't grow up with I didn't grow
up with cats so I didn't know and if
you're not familiar with cats let me
tell you this right now there's a
hairball it's not like in the cartoons
because that's what I was expecting
right I thought the cat was just gonna
kind of go am and then a tumbleweed blow
away or someone know a couple weeks
after we move in I wake up one morning
and Eddie is on my pillow he's right in
front of my face he's doing that stupid
thing cats do with his feet you know
he's like
I'll wake up to this I'm like wha
you trying to hypnotize me what is this
and then all of a sudden he starts to he
just starts going oh I thought he was
trying to talk to me I'm freaking out
I'm like what is it Eddie is there
trouble
you can be pulled out of well and then
all the sudden out of nowhere this wet
disgusting very glop of I after births
like Rockets out of his mouth right in
front of my face
here's the craziest thing was getting
even break eye contact with me as it
came out he's just like
Oh
let's break it out of my god and he just
went to the bathroom out of his mouth
and you're putting the food in the wrong
end sweetheart you're gonna read the bag
then he just wanders okay I'm out of
here
have fun cleaning that hot mess up I'm
gonna go hide into the dress or make
noises for three days
you